本字幕由大家字幕组原创翻译制作，仅供学习，禁止用于任何商业盈利行为。若因私自散布传播造成法律问题，本字幕组概不负责。更多影视请搜索并关注新浪微博@大家字幕组。
大家以后能不能把小孩儿赶到
Can we please try and shoo the toddlers away
离眼镜架远点的地方
From the sunglasses stand?
我知道他们喜欢在那儿晃悠
I know that's where they all like to go,
但我们真的损失了很多
But we're getting a lot of damage there.
EVERYONE
还有酸奶架的底层
Also from the lower yogurts.
关注新浪微博
@大家字幕组
扫扫加微信
那些小孩真的很喜欢把手指插进去
They tend to just want to put their fingers in.
你跟蒂娜有什么情况吗?
Something going on with you and Dina?
大家字幕组
微 信 关 注
dajiazimuzu
什么情况? 没有啊
No. What? No.
dajiazimuzu
我也不知道 但你俩一直
I don't know, man, you guys are exchanging
扫扫加微信
在偷瞄对方
Little peek-a-boo glances,
我看着老不舒服了
And it's making me uncomfortable.
dajiazimuzu
扫扫加微信
大家字幕组
好吧 你记得那次
Okay. The other night,
我们被锁在这儿了吧
When we were all locked in the store,
蒂娜貌似向我投怀送抱了
Dina kind of...Came on to me.
哇
Wow.
原来蒂娜喜欢小白脸类型的啊
I didn't know Dina was into fancy little porcelain doll-men.
所以 在抓到这只浣熊之前
So, while we haven't caught the raccoon yet,
咱们应该开始了解了解
I do feel that we're starting to have a better understanding
它的作案模式
Of his patterns.
你从了?
So, you tap that?
没有 我觉得挺不舒服的
No, I felt bad.
所以我告诉她她是我的上司
And I told her that I wasn't comfortable
所以我们不应该在一起
Dating a supervisor,
她对这点没什么异议
And she was cool with it.
聪明
Quick thinking.
接下来
Moving on,
蒂娜要公布一个消息
One final announcement from Dina.
这个决定将立即生效
effective immediately,
我将不再担任副经理
I will be stepping down from my position
今天开始我将成为一个普通的员工
Of assistant manager to associate level
因为我需要为自己私人的事情...腾些空间
So that I may concentrate on...Personal matters.
我想我能代表大家发言
Well, I think I speak for everyone
我们将会
When I say that's really, really sad.
非常想念你
I know that I'm gonna miss
和你经常性的批评及唠叨
Your constant criticism of me a lot.
我也会想念那个的
I'm gonna miss that too.
你确定我们不能做点什么来让你改变主意么?
Sure there's nothing we can say to make you stay?
嗯 你知道 总会有--
Well, you know, there's always--
哦 太遗憾了
Oh, too bad, so sad.
好的 大家再愉快的聊会儿天吧
Well, let's have an extra fun chant.
来 大家 说茄子!
Come on, give me a C!
茄子!
C!
好嗨森的感觉 嘴咧的停不下来了
Why can't I stop smiling?
超级商店
第一季 第十集
大家字幕组 欢乐出品
真不敢相信她竟然要降职
I can't believe she's stepping down.
翻译  巴西  笨笨  苏沐秋
嗯 我特好奇她私人的事情到底是什么
Hmm. I wonder what her personal matters could be.
翻译  没存在感的人  Davion
嘿 乔纳 你知道吗
Hey, Jonah. You got any ideas?
我? 不呀 我怎么会-- 总之我不知道
Me? No, I don't-- mm-mm.
校对  糖糖  苏沐秋  苹果酒
她的鸟没事吧?
Are her birds okay?
有谁查过实时网络相机么?
Has anybody checked the live webcam?
时间轴  西子耶
你们说她会不会是有什么赌债之类的
Maybe she has gambling debts and she had to take time off
特效  福娃  西子耶
然后得空出时间帮债主做事情啊
To do favors for the mob boss that she owes money to.
压制  冰岛
也有可能是别的事情啦
or maybe it's something else.
我主要好奇谁会接管她的职位
No, I wonder who's gonna replace her.
许多人都觉得应该让我来
A lot of people have been suggesting it should be me.
民意难违啊
Kind of a groundswell.
她在几周前的确是说过
You know, she did mention a few weeks ago
她祖母生病了
That her grandmother was sick.
哦 太好了
Oh, that's great!
呃 我的意思不是-- 呃...
No, I didn't mean-- no, it's, uh...
我是说 你们懂的 如果我那么老了
I was just saying, you know, like, if I get that age,
还不如直接把我枪毙了呢
Somebody put a bullet in me.
报告 我来就位了
I'm here, reporting for duty.
哦 你要在这儿工作?
Oh, you're gonna be working here?
跟我一起?
With me?
是的 但我不想让你感到尴尬
Yep. But I don't want this to be awkward for you
因为我曾经是你的上司
Just because I used to be above you,
你现在是老大了
So go ahead, boss lady.
告诉我应该干嘛吧
Tell me what to do.
哦 好吧 我是老大
Okay, well, I'm the boss now,
你最好乖乖听我的话
So you better do what I say.
我可以开这个玩笑 你不行
I make that joke. You don't make that joke.
好的 要从哪里开始你? 哇 看看这些五颜六色的
Okay, where do we start? Look at all these fun colors.
嘿 格林 你想见我?
Hey, Glenn, you wanted to see me?
艾米 来看看窗外的风景
Amy, come look out this window with me.
大多数人看到的只是个卸货区
See, most people would see a loading dock,
而我看到的却是--
But I see a--
我不想当副经理
I don't want to be assistant manager.
但是你都没看窗外呢
But you didn't even look out the window.
我知道 我真的很感激你的提议 真的
I know. Look, I really appreciate the offer, I do.
但这份工作基本上就是更多的工作和不变的工资
But it's basically more work for the same amount of money.
你哈时候变得这么介意钱了?
Since when have you been in this for the money?
大概是从一开始吧
Pretty much from day one.
我现在真的很不稳定
Things are crazy for me right now.
我还在继续读夜校...
I'm taking these night college courses...
我真的不行
I can't.
好吧 那我再想想办法吧
Okay. I'll figure something out, I guess...
但最起码来这儿和我一起看看窗外吧
But at least come over and look out the window with me.
这真的是个很好的卸货区
It is a nice loading dock.
真的是个很牛的卸货区
It's a nice loading dock.
早上好 女士
Good morning, ma'am.
你想让自己看起来精神点儿么?
Do you want to not look so tired?
你的损失
Your loss.
嗨 你在哪儿来着?
Hey, you. Where have you been?
我--呃 你懂的 这地方这么大
Me--oh, big store. You know, I--
有时候我会遇到别人 我会问
Sometimes I'll run into people, and I'll say,
"嘿 你去度假了?"
"Hey, have you been on vacation?"
然后他们会说 "没有 我一直在这儿"
And they'll be like, "Nah, I was here the whole time."
就喜欢你这种观察力
I love how you observe things.
嗯 迪娜 听着 那个--
Yeah. Listen, Dina, the--
你喜欢吃意式烩饭么?
Do you like risotto?
我做的烩饭还挺不错的 我在想
I make a nice risotto. I was thinking
今天晚上你想过来么
If you wanted to come over later tonight,
我可以做一些
I could make us some.
而且我的蓝牙上还存着"火爆教头草地兵"哦
And I have "Hoosiers" On blu-ray.
听起来很有意思
Well, that sounds like a great evening.
当然了 吉恩·哈克曼
Yeah. Gene hackman, so...
呃 迪娜 你真的觉得这是个好主意么?
Right. Dina, do you think this is really a good idea?
辞掉工作什么的
You know, the whole giving up your job thing?
哦 辞掉那份工作
Oh, quitting that job
是我做过的最好的决定
Was the best thing that's ever happened to me.
- 真的吗? - 当然了
- It was? - Heck, yeah.
我之前因为压力有过皮疹 还是亚伯拉罕林肯形状的
I was getting a stress rash in the shape of abraham lincoln.
但现在全没了
But now it's disappearing.
上面的部分几乎全都没了
I mean, his hat's almost completely gone.
我干嘛要说这些呢?
Why am I going on about it?
你马上就可以亲眼看到了
I mean, you're gonna see it soon enough.
呃...
Um...
但...
But...
说真的 我需要一些改变
I needed a change, honestly.
自从我祖母死后 我过的一直都很枯燥
Ever since my nana died, I've just been in such a rut.
哦 我很抱歉
Oh, no, I'm s-- I didn't--I'm so sorry.
她是个和蔼的老太太
Yeah, sweet lady.
但现在也很好
But it was probably for the best, though.
- 当然了 - 她要是在的话
- I'm sure. - I mean, she would not
应该不会接受
Have been cool with the whole--
我不知道要怎么说--
I don't really know how else to say it--
这段感情里的犹太人的成分
Jewishness of this relationship.
这段感情
Uh, the relationship
正是我们应该谈谈的
Is something that we should talk about.
嗯 对 你知道我不是一个没有安全感的人
Yeah. You know, I'm not normally an insecure person,
但是现在都说开 我得告诉你
but now that it's all out in the open, I gotta tell you,
有几次我在想
There was a couple of times where I thought,
我是不是得妄想症了? 他还爱我吗?
Am I being delusional? Does he even like me?
我觉得他还爱我
Like, I think he does.
又或者他只是像个反社会的渣男一样在玩弄我?
Or is he just stringing me along like some sociopath?
嗯 不
yeah, no.
不 不 我可不是那样 我可不是精神病渣男
Nope, nope, that's not me. I'm not a psychopath.
- 反社会的渣男 - 有什么区别么?
- Sociopath. - What's even the difference?
精神病的人没有是非之心
A psychopath doesn't have a conscience.
反社会的人知道他做的是错的
A sociopath knows what he's doing is wrong
但是还是会做
but does it anyway.
今天晚上八点见?
8:00 tonight?
我肯定不能拒绝啊
I can't say no.
我讨厌看你离开 我喜欢看你慢慢走开
Hate to see you go, but love to watch you leave.
天哪 你看起来也精疲力尽的
God, you look exhausted too.
所以我发现 解决助理经历难题的答案一直
So I realized the answer to our assistant manager problem
就在我们眼前
Has been right in front of us, literally forever.
你想提拔默特尔?
You're gonna promote Myrtle?
我决定按资历提拔
I decided to promote based on seniority,
而且她都具备
and she has both kinds.
还有 她有领导的经验
Plus, she has leadership experience.
她主管着蓓尔美尔街烟厂
She was head switchboard operator
的总开关
For the pall mall cigarette company.
额 是 可是...
Uh, yeah, but...
或许你可以先面试其他人
Maybe you should interview some other people first.
我不擅长面试
Well, I'm not very good with interviews.
我喜欢我遇到的每个人
I like just about everybody I meet.
我实际上一点标准都没有
I have virtually no standards.
好的 我是可以帮你找人
Okay, well, I could help you find someone.
但是你已经把工作给默特尔了
That is, if you haven't already offered myrtle the job.
不...
No...
我确实说了 但是她好像没听到
Well, I did, but I don't think she heard me.
所以 你没告诉她你其实不感兴趣
So, instead of just telling her you were not interested,
反而答应了去她家里吃意大利调味饭
You said you would go to her house to eat risotto
并且看吉恩 哈克曼激励了一整个小镇?
and watch Gene Hackman inspire a small town?
我不擅给坏消息啊
I'm not the bad news guy.
我从来都是好消息小天使
I'm the good news guy, you know?
"妮可有孩子了!”  "亚丁进校队了!”
"Nicole had a baby!" "Aden made varsity!"
"你听说过迪恩么? 他战胜了狼疮病"
"Did you hear about dean? He beat lupus!"
人们都喜欢从我这里听到好消息
People love hearing good news from me.
是 你在这方面是天才
Yeah, and you're totally unique in that way.
你应该强硬一点 看到那个男的了吗?
You need to toughen up. All right, see this dude?
不管我问什么 你都回答不
Whatever I ask you, the answer is no.
什么?
What?
-我要退掉这台搅拌机 -嗯 好
-I need to return this blender. - Oh, okay.
嗯 你有收据
Well, it looks like you've got the receipt,
搅拌机没被打开过
It has not been opened,
而且你是在十四天之内买的
and you purchased it within 14 days.
我可以退款给他吗?
Can I give him a refund?
抱歉 不能退
Sorry, no refunds.
你什么意思? 为什么不行?
What do you mean? Why not?
对啊 看上去挺正常的一次退货
Yeah, it seems like a pretty valid return.
我没什么好解释的
I do not have a good answer for that.
所以...
So...
我们给他一张积分卡怎么样?
Why don't we give him store credit?
- 这个对你有用么? - 嗯 可以
- Would that work for you? - Yeah, that's fine.
没有积分卡
No store credit.
我要和你们经理谈
I'd like to speak to your manager.
不行
No.
我们还会再见的
You haven't seen the last of me.
为什么这么做?
So what was the point of that?
不知道 我太无聊了
I don't know. I'm bored.
好的女士 我一定要强调这个
All right, ma'am. I cannot stress this enough.
你一定一定不能动
You need to be...So still.
就像...雕塑那样
Like a...Statue.
迪娜? 这种离眼睛这么近的工作
Dina? Do you want me to take over anything
你确定不要交给我吗?
Near the eyes?
不 我可以 实践出真知
Nope. I'm fine. Learning on the job.
但是她的眼睛这么美
Her eyes are so pretty, though.
我在想
I'm almost wondering,
是不是根本不用帮她画眼线呢?
What if you don't do any eyeliner at all?
我们得想办法让别人注意不到
Well, we've got to do something to draw attention
她的那个下巴啊
away from that chin.
我说了 别动
I said don't move.
或者你想让我把你绑在椅子上?
Or do you want me to strap you into this chair?
别看他 她现在帮不了你
Don't look at her. She can't help you right now.
狮子的力量
Strength of a lion.
看上去
Okay, this seems like something
这个我得围观一下
I need to know more about.
我在为应聘经理助理
Oh, I'm working on my presentation
的面试做准备
For assistant manager.
我想向他们展示我有狮子般的力量
I'm want to show them that I have the strength of a lion,
海豚的智慧
The intelligence of a dolphin,
还有工蚁般的决心
And the determination of a worker ant.
这个呢是我变成兔子的样子
And this is just what I look like on a rabbit.
我被说服了 但是...你要准备什么来
I'm sold, but... What are you gonna do
作为面试的才艺表演呢?
For the talent portion of the interview?
才艺表演?
Talent portion?
那看来我们有的忙了
I see we got some work to do.
我们开门见山好了
Okay, so, let's address the elephant in the room.
为什么堂堂药一个药剂师会想屈尊做一个经理助理呢？
Why does a pharmacist want to slum it as an assistant manager?
我是说 这是个恶作剧吧？ 是不是还有摄像机在拍我？
I mean, is this a prank show? Is there a camera watching?
是在考验我们吗?
Are we being plunked?
只是
Just...
事实上 我需要休息一下
Truth is, I need a break.
你有没有经历过 你紧紧握着一个临死的人的手
Have you ever held a dying man's hand in yours
而你却要要告诉他
While you had to tell him
你的奖励积分不能用于你的治疗费用
That we don't accept rewards points for his medication?
而他恰恰在听到这个消息后离去了
He literally died while I was holding his hand.
我不觉得有这回事
I don't think that's true.
那我想我们永远不会知道了
Well, I guess we'll never know.
听我说 桑德拉 我很佩服
I got to say, Sandra, I am impressed.
我没想到你也会对这个职位感兴趣
I did not expect you to be interested in this job,
你应该积极主动地坚持下去
But way to go, showing initiative.
你是对的 太抱歉了
You're right. I'm sorry.
我就不该来的
I shouldn't have come here.
哦 对不起
Ow! Sorry.
抱歉
Sorry.
是因为那些耳机吗？
Is this about the headphones?
-什么耳机? -哦 没什么
-What headphones? -Oh! I don't know.
我是说 我可没拿
I mean, I didn't take them.
可能只是他们忘了把耳机放进手推车里了
They probably forgot to load them on the truck.
没错就是这样
Right.
我是说 我们得考虑那是不是被偷的
I mean, if that's what was stolen.
当我们我们不知道事实到底是什么的时候
We don't know if something was, first.
这应该是我们第一个要问的问题
That should be the first question we ask,
在我们 指控别人之前
Before we make... Accusations.
-这是你的家人吗? -是的
-Is this your family? -Oh, yeah.
他们看起来真清纯
They're so clean.
你的简历上说你有丰富的照看孩子的经历
Your resume says you have a lot of experience babysitting.
事实上 上面只写了 “看”孩子
Actually, it just says, "Watching kids."
EVERYONE
大家字幕组
我说一下的条件 我要基本工资上调40%
Here's what I'm gonna need. I'll need a 40% salary bump,
大家字幕组
公司车辆的使用权
Access to a company car--
这个职位享有优先认股权吗？
Does the position come with stock options?
-额 -是这样的
-Um... -You know what,
大家字幕组
还是让我回答吧
Let me answer that.
这个职位享有优先认股权
The position will be coming with stock options.
当我小的时候
When I was a teenager,
有一次我撞坏了我爸的汉德森
I crashed my father's hudson super
还把责任推到一个中国人身上
And blamed it on a Chinese.
额 那简单谈谈你三个最大的缺点吧
Okay, and what about your three greatest weaknesses?
如果你们不相信的话 那你们为什么不查查录像带
If you don't believe me, then why don't you
去查录像带好吧？ 去查呀 伙计
Go check the tapes, okay? Just check the tapes, man.
全在录像带里 去查呀
It's all in the tapes. Check the tapes.
查录像带 查录像带
Check the tapes. Check the tapes.
好吧 我们会的
Yeah, all right, we will.
你们真的把我们都录在录像带里了？
You guys actually tape us?
那你们真是太刻薄了
That's so messed up.
让我事情简化一下吧
Let me make this very easy for you.
我会给你们五秒钟时间思考
I'm gonna give you five seconds to make a decision,
之后我就走人
And then I walk.
五...四…
Five...Four...
这孩子眼睛毫无生气
This one's eyes are dead,
但是这个孩子的却炯炯有神
But this one's eyes are alive.
-你叫她什么？ -哦 她叫...
-What do you call her? -Oh, her name is--
-千万别告诉他她的名字 -好吧
-Do not tell him her name. -Okay.
好了 现在提议取消
nope--offer's off the table.
是你搞砸了它
You blew it.
-唉 我就知道 -额 那太遗憾了
-Oh, I knew it. -Oh, well, so sad.
总之还是感谢你能抽出时间
Thanks for coming in anyway.
然而 你真是幸运
But it's your lucky day.
我再给你一个机会
I'm gonna give you one more chance.
现在我给你们双倍的时间
Now my demands are doubled.
好了 十 九
Okay--ten, nine...
不 马特奥 你的未来不属于这里
No, Mateo, your future is not here,
不属于马尼拉
In Manila...
它属于美利坚
It lies in America.
登船时间! 下一站:埃利斯岛
All aboard! Next stop, ellis island.
罗德里格 往后退点 你离边缘太近了
No, Rodrigo, stand back. You're too close to the edge.
你会摔下去的!
You'll fall!
不 马特奥 我想做第一个触碰到
No, Mateo, I want to be the first to touch...
自由女神的男人!
Lady libertyyyyyyyy...
哦天啊 你又说对了 马特奥 你总是能说着！
Oh, my god, you were right, Mateo--you're always right!
我还剩好多还没演完呢
It actually goes on for much longer.
这就够了 我很喜欢
I've seen enough. I like it.
你有料
You got the steak.
现在需要好好加工一下
Now it's time to make it sizzle.
谢谢惠顾云九
Thank you so much for shopping at cloud 9.
祝你有美好的一天
Have a heavenly day.
下一位— 迪娜
Next custom-- Dina.
-嘿 -嘿
-Hey. -Hey.
只是到了我休息的时候
Just on my break,
我来买点杂七杂八的东西
So I thought I'd pick up a couple odds and ends.
很好 很好
Cool, cool.
超棒的意大利肉汁烩饭
Famous risotto.
一盒巧克力—你永远不知道下一颗是什么味
Box of chocolates--you never know what you're gonna get.
多样尺寸
Multiple sizes.
你没法预料需要用哪个尺寸的
You never know what you're gonna get.
不好意思 你能再解释一遍这些顺序吗
I'm sorry, can you explain the order again?
如果你从左到右看
As you go from left to right,
一个比一个差劲
Then each one is worse than the one before it.
-好的 -但是
- Okay. - But,
如果你从右往左看
If you go from right to left,
那么… 额 一个比一个差劲
Then...Each one is worse than the one before it.
也许是你的标准太高了
Maybe your standards are too high.
毕竟 我们只是一个零售百货超市
I mean, we're a retail department store.
我们又不是在招英国兰国王
We're not hiring the king of England here.
我只是不想招一些
I just don't want to hire someone
让我们非常蛋疼的人
who's gonna make our daily lives miserable.
艾米 来和我一起看看窗外
Amy, come have a look out the window with me.
在危急时刻
You know, in times of crisis,
好人总是会做些应做的事情...
Good people do what needs to be done, and...
艾米! 你是走了还是去嘘嘘?
Amy! Are you leaving or just peeing?
走了
Leaving.
哦 那我就不用等你了
Okay. Just wanted to know if I should wait.
不用客气
You're so welcome.
我们居然重新使用这些东西
I can't believe we reuse this stuff.
看起来好不卫生
Doesn't seem sanitary.
一般这上面不会有血的
Well, there's usually not so much blood on them.
哪怕有点血...
Well, even a little bit of blood...
从来就没有过!
There's never any blood!
我能和你谈谈吗?
Hey, can I talk to you for a second...
就我俩...
Privately?
你想和我怎么谈都行
Yeah, you can talk to me whatever way you like.
来我办公室
Step into my office.
好
Okay.
挺好的 再街头风一点
Good. More street.
马特奥要当助理经理!
Mateo for assistant manager!
搞定!
Mew mew mew. Peace!
我觉得你理想能更远大一点
I think you can go bigger.
迪娜...
Okay, look. Dina...
这有点难说出口...
This-this is tricky, um...
这不是旅馆!
Okay! It's not a motel.
今天真是浪漫满屋
Love's just in the air today, I guess.
迪娜...
Yeah, listen. Dina, the...
我想和你说一些事
There are some things that I wanted to say to you,
我纠结了很久了
And I've been having a tough time saying it,
所以我把他们录在手机里
So I recorded it on my phone
我现在要播放了...
and I would like to play it...
放轻松
Hey, relax.
无论是什么 宝宝俩一起面对
Whatever it is, we will deal with it together, as a couple.
好 我要... 我要按播放了哈
Okay, I'm just gonna... I'm gonna press play, okay?
按下去... 按下去
Just-just force myself to press play.
嘎啦苹果 鹰嘴豆泥 甘蓝脆片 不不不
Gala apples, hummus, kale chips. Oh, no, no, no. No, no, no.
不是... 不是这个
That's not... that's not it.
- 没关系的 - 放错了
- Hey, it's okay. - It's the wrong voice memo.
所有事一开始都会很尴尬
Everything's awkward in the beginning, you know?
但你继续深入了解对方...
When you're still getting to know someone...
- 我好像用日期分类了 - 比如亲个小嘴
- Maybe if I sort by date. - Before you've even kissed.
- 稍等一下 - 也许我们应该
- Just one second. - Maybe we should just
- 把这步先解决了 - 哪步?
- get that part out of the way. - What part?
这步
This part.
你的牙太可口了
Oh, your teeth taste so good.
谢谢...
Thank y...
迪娜 我很抱歉
Dina, I'm so sorry,
但我对你没有那种感觉
but I don't have the se feelings for you.
对不起
Oh, I'm sorry.
我觉得在一发不可收拾之前
I felt like I need to tell you
我得向你坦白...
before either of us did anything that we regret..
我... 这不是... 我非常抱歉...
I'm... that wasn't... I'm so sorry...
这手机外放可真是棒
That phone has a really good speaker on it.
你是个好人 我真的很想和你做朋友...
An amazing person, and your friendship means so much...
迪娜 迪娜!
Dina. Dina!
他们走了
Okay, they're gone.
你敢信... 那男的真是个怂包!
Wow, can you believe... that guy was a wuss!
就是 渣男一个 稍微弯一点
Yeah, he was the worst. Bend down a little more.
这样镜子里能看到我自己
I'm trying to look at mysef in the mirror.
我应该和她说点什么
I should say something to her.
但你刚用录音拒绝了她
But you just broke up with the lady over voice memo.
还是让她冷静一下比较好吧
Maybe just let her chill out for a little bit.
不行 我不能就此不管了
You know what? I'm not leaving it like this.
别 别 别啊...
Whoa, whoa, hey, hey, no, no, no, don't...
顾客们 请注意
Attention, shoppers:
你是不是要做一些可能会后悔的事情了?
Are you about to do something you might regret?
云九建议你三思而行
We here at cloud 9 encourage you to reconsider.
扪心自问
Just ask yourself,
"我这么做是为了帮助别人
"Am I doing this to help someone else
或者只是让自己心里好受点?"
or to make myself feel better?"
对 家庭用品还没送过来
Yeah, I'm still waiting on a shipment for housewares.
格林?
Hey, Glenn?
排班表今天不是该出了吗?
Weren't the shift schedules supposed to come out today?
恩 我在打电话
Yeah, I'm on the phone.
我只想知道我明天要上班吗?
Okay, I just need to know if I should come in tomorrow.
恩 明天过来 当然...
Yeah, come in tomorrow. Sure...
什么时间?
What time?
随便! 啥时候都行!
I don't care! Any time!
不不 我不是说送货时间
No, no, not anytime for the shipment.
喂?
Hello?
格林?
Hey, Glenn?
你还好吗?
Is everything okay?
没事 在这两头忙呢
Yeah, just trying to do two jobs here.
我觉得我要是能在我眨眼的时候
I think if I can just start sleeping in tiny little bursts
顺便小睡一会就好了
while I'm already blinking
所以你要试着自己把所有的活都干了?
So, you're gonna try and do both of these jobs yourself?
-你疯了吧 -想想如果有人
-That's crazy. - What if someone had told
告诉本 阿夫雷克 他不能自导自演了?
Ben Affleck that he couldn't act and direct?
我们永远也别想看到那部关于伊朗的片子了
Then we never would've had that movie about Iran,
或者别的啥 不好意思 我没看过别的片子
or, whatever... I’m sorry, I never saw it.
- 格林 - 啥米?
- Glenn! - What?
这工作我做了
I'll take the job.
太感谢了
Oh, thank you!
你不知道这活有多难干
You have no idea how hard this has been.
不过越干我越佩服
Though it has dramatically increased
本 阿夫雷克
my respect for Ben Affleck.
今天完全没按着我的计划来
Well, today didn't work out exactly as I planned.
也别问了 不关你的事
Don't bother asking for details. It's none of your business.
但是我依然制霸了化妆品区
But I did kill it in cosmetics.
是啊 当然了
Yeah, you sure did.
你到是需要再提高一下
You could improve, though.
明天我要带把手动榨汁器来
I'm gonna bring a grip squeezer tomorrow.
你得固定好他们的脸
You need to control their faces more.
嘿 迪娜 听我说
Hey, Dina, listen.
我知道可能我不该再提了
I know I should probably leave this alone,
但是我真的想就我处理这些事的方式
But I just wanted to say I'm really sorry
道个歉
About the way I handled everything.
我是说 我 你是个了不起的人
I mean, I... you're an amazing person.
没事的 你没必要说这些
It's fine. You don't have to do this.
不 我要说 因为这是我的真心话 真的
No, I do, because I mean it. I mean it.
你也知道 你一定会遇到一个很棒的人
You know, you're gonna meet someone terrific,
我只是希望你和我能...
And I just hope you and I can...
- 嘿 宝贝大妈 - 嘿 你准备好了?
- Hey, Mama. - Hey, you ready?
好了 我太激动了 我从没看到过 《球场雄心》
Yeah, I'm psyched. I've never seen "Hoosiers."
这片一定会改变你的人生 走吧
It'll change your life. Let's go.
下手好快啊
That was fast.
没必要这么尴尬 好吗?
Look, this doesn't have to be weird, okay?
只是咱俩不合适 当然了 你很帅
It just didn't work out. Sure, you're cute,
但是 帅哥太多了
But there’s, there's a lot of cute around.
明天见吧
See you tomorrow.
嘿 我问一句 你不讨厌鸟吧?
Oh, hey, I should ask, are you okay with birds?
我养了很多鸟
I have a lot of birds.
我真的很感激 艾米
I really appreciate it, Amy,
我知道这份工作可能比较艰苦
And I know the job might be tough,
但是有很多福利
but there are a lot of perks,
比如5%的员工折扣
like 5% additional discount,
提供再教育的补贴
Financial aid for continuing education,
还有 近一点的停车位
And, and a closer parking spot.
- 等等 你说有啥? - 停车位
- Wait, what? - Yeah.
你可以停我车旁边
You'll be parking next to me.
以后麻烦开门的时候注意啦
Open your door with caution, please.
不 他们会帮我付大学学费?
No, they help you pay for college classes?
是啊 但估计只付一半
Oh, yeah, but I think only half.
一半啊...
Half...
太棒了
Yes!
来面试助理经理的是
Interviewing for assistant manager,
马特奥...
Mateo...
费尔南多...
Fernando...
阿基诺...
Aquino...
李旺诺!
Liwanag!
准备好了吗?
Are you ready?
马特奥 我很抱歉 我刚把职位给了艾米
Mateo, I'm sorry, I just offered the job to Amy.
我不知道你也有意向
I didn't know you were interested.
EVERYONE
大家字幕组
本字幕由大家字幕组原创翻译
仅供学习使用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
彼以国士待我 我以国士待之
用过免费优质字幕服务 而又有能力的人
有义务将这个免费服务做下去
若有心加入我们
请联系QQ群：428872140
我知道了
I see.
大家字幕组
恭喜
Congratulations.
谢谢你
Thank you.
大家字幕组